elon.io 2017-07-11

# Elon.io | Privacy policy

We use technologies like cookies (small files stored on your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system and IP address. 

We also may collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name, address, phone number or email address. With your permission, we may also access other personal information on your device, such as your phone book, calendar or messages, in order to provide services to you. If authorized by you, we may also access profile and other information from services like Facebook. 

Our systems may associate this personal information with your activities in the course of providing service to you (such as pages you view or things you click on or search for). 

We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information. 

We do not collect, use or share your precise geographic location. 

We remove personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, email or phone number) and other preferences associated with your account promptly after you delete your account. We may retain other data indefinitely. 

We generally do not share personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email or phone) with other companies. 

We measure conversions from Google and Facebook advertisements and send this information to Google and Facebook to optimize the performance of our advertisements. We do not allow any other advertising companies to collect data through our service for ad targeting. 

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us at legal@elon.io 

Google Analytics and Facebook may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user. No other companies have access to any data. 

We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. This includes utilizing Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the personal information you input. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error. 

Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business. 

To operate the service, we also may make identifiable and anonymous information available to third parties in these limited circumstances: (1) with your express consent, (2) when we have a good faith belief it is required by law, (3) when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to protect our rights or property, or (4) to any successor or purchaser in a merger, acquisition, liquidation, dissolution or sale of assets. Your consent will not be required for disclosure in these cases, but we will attempt to notify you, to the extent permitted by law to do so. 

This privacy policy was last updated on September 9, 2015. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email, push notification or text. 

This privacy policy is created using [PrivacyChoice](http://www.privacychoice.org/resources) licensed under a [Creative Commons license](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/2.0). 

Sign up to save your progress!
